

Victor ABIZEYIMANA

PERSONAL DETAILS

Father: SIBOMANA Maurdi **Mother:** NDIMBIREYEZU Patricie

DOB: 01/01/1993 **Sex:** Male

Marital Status: Single

CONTACTS

- svicky.shema@gmail.com
- **4** 0789032290
- facebook.com/vicky.cadet
- @vicky_abz

SKILLS

HTML CSS PHP Javascript

Node Js

Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator Adobe InDesign Adobe XD Sketch



















Hobbies and interests

I have a strong interest in visual arts beyond Creative design. I am also a skilled pianist, vocal coach, and guitarist. Additionally, I have an interest in interior design and enjoy reading about business, interior design and personal development.

Profile

Creative graphic designer and an ambitious problem solver with a passion for online businesses. Victor has a keen interest in technology, mobile applications and user experience. He is equipped with innovative ideas and a unique approach to developing designs for online websites, video, and advertising.

Solid understanding of marketing principles and advertising techniques. Great attention to detail and a talent for creating memorable visual designs.

Enthusiastic team player who is committed to delivering top results on time and within the budget.

Education

2018

Bachelor of Business Administration

University of Rwanda

2017

Training in Graphic Design

Lynda.com | udemy.com | Adobe Edex

2014

A2 in Math Physics and Computer Science

ES Kanombe/ Efotec

2010

O'Level

ESSA Ruhengeri



Primary School

EP Rubirizi

Work Experience

Inepu Limited _ _ _ _ _ _ _ 2017 - Present

Part Time,Web Developer

Responsible for working on a range of projects, designing appealing websites.

- Developing and maintaining the front end functionality of websites.
- Participating in discussions with clients to clarify what they want.
- Designing prototypes for apps and websites.
- Developing websites that have a consistent feel and look throughout all web properties.

T-Kay Investment _ _ _ _ _ _ **2018 - Present** *Graphic Designer*

- Develop Designs for Different customers
- Develop Marketing Graphics, Videos for Social Medias
- Run company's website.

Freelance _ _ _ _

- - - 2015 - 2017

I've worked with agencies, design studios and also taken on solo projects. The work has been primarily in the realms of design, Video making, Video editing.

References

- NYIBUHUNGIRO Pierre Bernard -- 0786 365 026 (pbernard@inepu.com)
 CEO @ Inepu Ltd
- ♦ NGARAMBE MUKUBA Thierry-- 0788 174 114 (ngarambethierry@gmail.com)
 Operation Manager @ T-Kay Investment Ltd

Declaration

I, Victor ABIZEYIMANA declare that the information given in this CV is sincere and complete to all my best of my knowledge and belief.